Guide to the Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Audio Collection ALBA.AUDIO.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Public Events, 1970-1999
  - VALB 50th Anniversary Dinner (NY Post, Music and Dramatic Reading; live recording) [tape 2 of 2] [Copy], Apr 7, 1986 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-159)
  - VALB 55th Anniversary Dinner (NY Post) [Master], Apr 26, 1992 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-160)
  - VALB 55th Anniversary Dinner (NY Post) [Copy], Apr 26, 1992 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-161)
- Series III: Music, 1976-2002.
  - "Espana, Vol. 1" (Commercial Release), 1976 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-162)
  - "Espana Vol. 2" (Commercial Release), 1976 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-163)
  - "La Internacional" (Commercial Release), 1977 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-164)
  - "Last American Heroes," by Harry Fisher's Son (original composition; home recording), undated (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-165)
  - "Ride On," Christy Moore (Commercial Release), 1987 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-166)
  - "Songs of the Spanish Civil War, Vol. #1 and Vol. #2" [tape copy of a Folkways recording], undated (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-167)
  - "We Had All the Good Songs," by Ross Altman (original composition; home recording), Aug 1987 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-168)
  - [International Brigade Songs] (copy of another recording), undated (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-169)
  - [Six Songs for Democracy Dixos de las Brigadas Internacionales] (tape copy of a record), undated (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-170)
  - [Songs for Democracy] (tape copy of a record), undated (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-171)
  - [Songs of the Lincoln Brigade] and "ILGWU - We Work, We Sing" (tape copy of a record), undated (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-172)
  - [Spanish Civil War Songs] (tape copy of a record), undated (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-173)
  - German and Italian Songs from the SCW (tape copy of a record; made by Tom Sarbaugh), Feb 2002 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-174)
  - Trip to Spain: Singing [Spanish and English] (Recorded by Blythe Allison Bennett), Oct 1986 (Drawer 5, Cassette 1-175)